There's, you know, mainly Jewish white men, and most of our school was not Jewish.
And they had control over our public school system over, like, the past 10 years,
purposely voting no on our school budget vote so that we would fail, and we lost about 3-2 schools.
Basically, through block voting, Orthodox Jews won enough seats to control the East Ramaphos School Board
and went on to eliminate hundreds of public school positions like teachers and social workers
while approving millions of taxpayer dollars to be spent on their children's religious private schools
ultimately gutting the public school system for the estimated 9,000 black and brown public school students
while diverting that money to their private religious schools.
They give us food that's rotten and it's cold, and it hurts our stomach.
I ask you to not take our music program away. I love playing an instrument. My brother would be crushed.
And the budget cuts were so devastating that in one instance, an elementary school shut down,
and the majority Jewish school board then voted to sell it to a Jewish yeshiva for pennies on the dollar.
Basically, the poorest, most vulnerable kids in these communities had their schools gutted and looted,
all by a majority Jewish school board whose kids didn't even attend public school.
We believe that some of the decisions that have been made by the board
have not been in the best interest of the public school community.
You don't like it? Find yourself another place to live.
You don't want to see you guys.